BRAC Additional Records 5488 C
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BRAC Additional Records
1921-1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees (BRAC)
5488 C
127 cubic feet
127 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Proposals, resolutions, convention proceedings, and meeting minutes
3120787
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 15, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 14, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees was organized in 1899, and it was the largest single railroad organization for employees who devoted a majority of their time to clerical work of any description including chief clerks, foremen, train announcers, gatemen, checkers; parcel, baggage, and storeroom employees; dock and pier workers; train and engine crew callers; timekeepers; paymasters; freight inspectors; rate and tariff compilers; weigh masters; ticket clerks and sellers; operators of all office and station equipment devices; telephone and switchboard operators; and all employees occupying or performing duties similar to those mentioned. After three months of experience in clerical work employees of both genders, with good moral character, became eligible for membership. The union secured increases in wages and better working conditions for its members.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5082: U.S. National Mediation Board Transcript of Hearings Regarding the BRAC 5086: U.S. National Mediation Board Transcripts Regarding New York Central Railroad Company and BRAC 5488: BRAC Records 5488 A: BRAC Chicago Files 5488 A & B mf: BRAC Guides on Microfilm 5488 B: BRAC Records 5488 D: BRAC Additional Records 5488 MB: BRAC Memorabilia 5735: BRAC Additional Records 6187: BRAC, Philadelphia Division, Union Local President Robert Curran Papers
Utility Workers Union of America; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States -- Sources; AFSCME; Air Line Dispatchers Association; Air Line Employees Association, International; Air Line Pilots Association; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; American Federation of Teachers; Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America; Amalgamated Transit Union; American Federation of Government Employees; American Federation of Musicians; Baking and Confectionery Workers; Boot and Shoe Workers Union; Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers International Union of America; Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.); Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes.; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees; Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters; Brotherhood Railway Carmen of America; Cigar Makers' International Union of America; Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Workers' International Union of America; Flight Engineers' International Association; Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union; Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America; International Association of Machinists; International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers, and Helpers; International Brotherhood of Bookbinders; International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers; International Chemical Workers Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; International Longshoremen's Association; International Printing, Pressmen's, and Assistants Union of America; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers; International Jewelry Workers Union; International Leather Goods, Plastics and Novelty Workers' Union; International Typographical Union; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers; Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America; International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America; International Woodworkers of America; Journeymen Barbers, Hairdressers, Cosmetologists, and Proprietors' International Union of America; Journeymen Stone Cutters' Association; Metal Polishers, Buffers, Platers & Helpers International Union; National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (U.S.); National Maritime Union of America; Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union; Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen; Railroad Yardmasters of America; Seafarers' International Union of North America; Service Employees International Union; Sheet Metal Workers' International Association; Switchmen's Union of North America; Textile Workers Union of America; Tobacco Workers International Union; Transportation-Communication Employees Union (U.S.); United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America; United Furniture Workers of America; United Garment Workers of America; United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America; United Mine Workers of America; United Papermakers and Paperworkers; United Steelworkers of America; United Transport Service Employees of America; United Transportation Union; Upholsterers' International Union of North America
3120787
- 203-71 (Box 1)
  - 1971 Grand Lodge Convention (Miami Beach, Florida) - Delegates., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Resolutions Submitted to the Twenty Fourth Regular and Tenth Quadrennial Convention, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Scope and Contents
    April 10, 1971. Bound.
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Proposed Amendments to the Grand Lodge Constitution, Statutes for the Government of Lodges, and Protective Laws - Twenty Fourth Regular Convention, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    May 6, 1971. Bound.
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Proposed Amendments to the Constitution, Statutes for the Government of Lodges, and Protective Laws - Twenty Fourth Regular Convention, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    May 7, 1971. Bound.
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Proceedings of the Twenty Fourth Regular and Tenth Quadrennial Convention, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Monday and Tuesday, May 24-25 1971. Bound.
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Proceedings of the Twenty Fourth Regular and Tenth Quadrennial Convention, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Tuesday and Wednesday, May 25-26 1971. Bound.
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Proceedings of the Twenty Fourth Regular and Tenth Quadrennial Convention, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Wednesday and Thursday, May 26-27 1971. Bound.
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Proceedings of the twenty Fourth Regular and Tenth Quadrennial Convention, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Friday, May 28, 1971. Bound.
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Proceedings of the Twenty Fourth Regular and Tenth Quadrennial Convention, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Friday and Saturday, May 28-29, 1971. Bound.
  - 1971 Grand Lodge Convention (Miami Beach, Florida) - Appointments and Acknowledgements (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1971 Grand Lodge Convention - Resolutions: Post-Convention Disposition (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Convention - Grand Lodge Officers Report to the Convention, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Grand Lodge Convention - International President's Report, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1971 Grand Lodge Convention - Committee on Finance, Salaries, Mileage, and Per Diem (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1971 Grand Lodge Convention (Miami Beach, Florida)- Railroad Retirement and Unemployment Insurance Committee (Box 1, Folder 15)
    April 15, 1971. Convention on May 23, 1971.
  - 1971 Convention Revolution - 201 Structure Committee, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    November 1972
  - 1971 Brotherhood Convention (Miami Beach, Florida) - Committees (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Found Empty December 15, 2014
  - Resolutions Acknowledged - Lodges 0-599 (State Legislation and Structure Communications), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Resolutions Acknowledged - Lodges 600-1199 (State Legislation and Structure Communications), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Resolutions Acknowledged - Lodges 1200-3054 (State Legislation and Structure Communications), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Resolutions Acknowledged - System Boards, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Grand Lodge Convention - Dues Protest, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    July 21, 1971-August 31, 1971
  - Grand Lodge Convention - Dues Protest, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    September 1971
  - Grand Lodge Convention - Dues Protest, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    September 1, 1971-December 3, 1971
  - Grand Lodge Convention - Dues Protest, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    November 1971
- 71 (Box 2)
  - Grand Lodge Convention (General) - May 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Grand Lodge Convention, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    May 1971
  - Grand Lodge Convention (Miami Beach, Florida) - Appointments and Acknowledgements, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Grand Lodge Convention (1971) - Appointments (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1971 Brotherhood Convention - Committees (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1971 Brotherhood Convention (Miami Beach, Florida) - Committees (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Conventions - Miscellaneous Information, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Important Convention Information (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Grand Lodge Convention - Local Convention Committee (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1971 Grand Lodge Convention (Miami Beach, Florida) - Local Convention Committee (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - BRAC 1971 Convention - No Appointments (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - BRAC Convention 1971 - Appointments (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - BRAC 1971 Convention - Appointed (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Resolutions Submitted to Convention (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1971 Convention - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Laws Committee Report 2.0 and 2.0A (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Laws Committee Opening Remarks and Reports 1-10 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Laws Committee Reports 11-19 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Laws Committee Reports 31-43 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1971 Convention Notes (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 1971 Convention Delegates (Box 2, Folder 15)
- 71 (Box 3)
  - Grand Lodge Convention - Dues Protests, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    June 20, 1971-July 1971
  - Grand Lodge Convention - Dues Protests, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    June 4-29, 1971
  - Grand Lodge Convention - Dues Protests, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Retirement (5510655), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    File 1.
  - Retirement (551-655), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    File 2
  - Retirement (551-655), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    File 3
  - Retirement (551-655), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    File 4
  - Retirement (551-655), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    File 5
  - Retirement (551-655), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    File 6
  - Retirement (551-655), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    File 7
  - Resolutions - Index and Classification (Box 3, Folder 11)
    No date
  - Resolutions - Index and Classification (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Copy of Previous File. No date.
  - Correspondence - R. Huber, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Printed Report of Committee on Constitution and Laws and Other Documents, 1967-1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Other Documents: Constitutions and By-Laws, Resolutions, Proposed Amendments, and Convention Proceedings
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Committee on Grand Lodge Constitution and Laws, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    May 1971. Bound.
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Resolutions Submitted to the Twenty Fourth Regular and Tenth Quadrennial Convention, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Resolutions Submitted to the Twenty Fourth Regular and Tenth Quadrennial Convention, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Resolutions Submitted to the Twenty Fourth Regular and Tenth Quadrennial Convention, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Resolutions Submitted to the Twenty Fourth Regular and Tenth Quadrennial Convention, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Resolutions Submitted to the Twenty Fourth Regular and Tenth Quadrennial Convention, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Resolutions Submitted to the Twenty Fourth Regular and Tenth Quadrennial Convention, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Resolutions Submitted to the Twenty Fourth Regular and Tenth Quadrennial Convention, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks - Resolutions Submitted to the Twenty Fourth Regular and Tenth Quadrennial Convention, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Grand Lodge Convention, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Grand Lodge - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Laws Committee - Reports 21-30, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- 204 - 1-22 (Box 4)
  - Labor Organizations - Air Line Pilots Association, 1961-1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    July 1, 1961-October 14, 1965
  - Labor Organizations - Baking and Confectionery Workers, 1924-1970 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    January 1924-May 1, 1970. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Labor Organizations - Journey Barbers, Hairdressers, Cosmetologists, and Proprietors International Union of America, 1932-1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Labor Organizations - International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers, and Helpers, 1925-1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Includes Bound Materials.
  - Labor Organizations - International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, 1930-1968 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Labor Organizations - International Union of Brewery Workers, 1922-1970 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    January 1, 1922-August 17, 1970
  - Labor Organizations - Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers International Union, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Includes Bound Materials. Old File Not Located.
  - Labor Organizations - Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, 1925-1971 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Labor Organizations - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    January 1, 1960-February 10, 1961
  - Labor Organizations - Cigar Makers International Union of America, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    June-July 1964
  - Labor Organizations - Amalgamated Clothing Workers, 1960-1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    January 1, 1960-November 16, 1972. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Labor Organizations - Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, 1963-1969 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    January 1, 1963-March 24, 1969. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Labor Organizations - Distillery, Rectifying, Wine and Allied Worker's International Union of America, 1938-1970 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Labor Organizations - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1955-1970 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Labor Organizations - Engineers, Architects, and Draftsmen, International, 1938-1970 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Labor Organizations - Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1965-1970 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    January 1, 1965-April 22, 1970. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Labor Organizations - National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association, 1931-1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Labor Organizations - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    October 1, 1967-1968
  - Labor Organizations - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    January 1, 1967-September 30, 1967
  - Labor Organizations - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    January 16-December 31, 1966
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen - Health and Welfare Program - Travelers' Insurance, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Includes Bound Materials
- 23-53 (Box 5)
  - Labor Organizations - International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1933-1970 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Labor Organizations - Flight Engineers International Association, 1962-1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Labor Organizations - International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, 1964-1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Labor Organizations - United Garment Workers of America, 1960-1967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Labor Organizations - American Federation of Government Employees, 1947-1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    April 1947-March 3, 1971
  - Labor Organizations - Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders' International Union, 1954-1969 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    August 1954-June 5, 1969
  - Labor Organizations - Leather Workers International Union, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    January 1964
  - Labor Organizations - International Longshoremen's Association, 1963-1971 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    January 1, 1963-April 26, 1971
  - Labor Organizations - International Association of Machinists, 1963-1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    January 1, 1963-March 6, 1970. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Labor Organizations - International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots, 1923-1962 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Labor Organizations - United Mine Workers of America, 1953-1966 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    January 1, 1953-1966. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Labor Organizations - American Federation of Musicians, 1956-1970 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    January 1, 1956-July 1970. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Labor Organizations - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators, etcetera, 1960-1970 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    January 1, 1960-August 10, 1970
  - Labor Organizations - Papermakers and Paper Workers, 1960-1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    January 1, 1960-February 1970
  - Labor Organizations - United Papermakers and Paperworkers - Charter, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    March 6, 1957. Bound.
  - Labor Organizations - Railway Patrolmen's International Union, 1960-1968 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    January 1, 1960-November 19, 1968
  - Labor Organizations - Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1960-1967 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    January 1, 1960-June 1967
  - Labor Organizations - International Printing, Pressmen's, and Assistants Union of America, 1963-1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    January 1, 1963- February 1970
  - Labor Organizations - Railway Employees Department, 1965-1971 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    January 1, 1965-July 13, 1971
  - Labor Organizations - Railway Employees' Department - 1962 Rules Program, Railway Employees' Department (American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Labor Organizations - Seafarers International Union, 1964-1969 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    January 1, 1964-July 10, 1969
  - Labor Organizations - Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, 1950-1969 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Labor Organizations - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1952-1968 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Labor Organizations - United Steelworkers of America, 1963-1969 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    January 1, 1963-July 31, 1969. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Labor Organizations - Amalgamated Transit Union, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Labor Organizations - Amalgamated Transit Union, 1939-1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Labor Organizations - American Railway and Airway Supervisors Association, 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Labor Organizations - Switchmen's Union of North America, 1961-1967 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- 63- (Box 6)
  - Labor Organizations - United Transportation Union (Formerly Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen), 1963-1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    January 1, 1963- August 1973. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Labor Organizations - National Maritime Union of America, 1963-1968 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    January 1, 1963-December 1968
  - Charitable Organizations - General, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    May 19-December 1975
  - Charitable Organizations - General, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    September 1974-May 6, 1975
  - International Affairs - General, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    January 1-December 9, 1974
  - International Affairs - General, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - International Affairs - International Transport Workers Federation, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    July 1973-May 1974
  - Labor Newspaper - Annual and Special Meetings, 1967-1973 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    January 1, 1967-December 31, 1973
- 54-74 (Box 7)
  - Labor Organizations - American Federation of Teachers, 1957-1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    January 1, 1957-July 10, 1970. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Labor Organizations - Transportation-Communication Employees Union, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    January 1, 1967-December 31, 1969
  - Labor Organizations - Transportation-Communication Employees Union, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    June 1, 1965-December 31, 1966
  - Labor Organizations - Transportation-Communication Employees Union, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    June 1, 1964-May 31, 1965
  - Labor Organizations - Textile Workers Union of America, 1960-1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    January 1, 1960-December 17, 1970
  - Labor Workers - Tobacco Workers International Union, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Labor Organizations - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen - Political Education Committee (TPEL), 1965-1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Labor Organizations - United Transport Service Employees, 1948-1968 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    January 1, 1948-August 21, 1968
  - Labor Organizations - International Typographical Union, 1961-1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    January 1, 1961-March 24, 1970
  - Labor Organizations - Upholsterers International Union, 1956-1970 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    January 1, 1956-April 7, 1970. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Labor Organizations - United Railroad Operating Crafts, 1958-1971 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    August 22, 1958-February 10, 1971. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Labor Organizations - Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1963-1968 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    January 1, 1963-August 1968. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Reference Manual on the Mediation Agreement (Job Security), 1965 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    February 7, 1965
  - Labor Organizations - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1965-1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    January 1, 1965-1970. Includes Bound Materials.
  - Labor Organizations - Service Employees International Union, 1960-1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Labor Organizations - International Air Line Stewards and Stewardesses Association, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Labor Organizations - Air Line Dispatchers Association, 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- 75-100-end (Box 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railway Carmen - Air Line Employees Association (ALEA) and the Airline Dispatcher (ALDA), 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Labor Organizations - Air Line Employees Association, 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Labor Organizations - Boot and Shoe Workers' Union, 1963-1966 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Labor Organizations - International Chemical Workers Union, 1963-1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Labor Organizations - Communication Workers of America, 1962-1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Labor Organizations - International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, 1965-1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Labor Organizations - United Furniture Workers of America, 1964-1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Labor Organizations - Glass Bottle Blowers' Association of the United States and Canada, 1965-1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Labor Organizations - United Glass and Ceramic Workers of North America, 1964-1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Labor Organizations - International Jewelry Workers Union, 1965-1970 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Labor Organizations - International Leather Goods, Plastics, and Novelty Workers Union, 1963-1971 (Box 8, Folder 11)